- No problem. You want to try it? Yeah, that's good too.
- Wait, isn't that a frog?
- It's a frog!
- It's a frog! Oh, my God!
- I can smell it.
- I'm really going next time.
- What about the side? What about the side?
- Amis is in Malaysia!
Amis is Malaysia! Amis is Malaysia!
Hey everybody!
We're going to a, uh, night market tonight?
Yes, the night market.
We're going to the, uh, night market.
Let's see how far the three of us can go for 1,000 yen.
I'm looking forward to it!
Yes, so first of all
I'll give you this 1,000 yen.
Thank you for buying it.
No, no, no. Everyone's.
Everyone's redeeming this
I'd like to buy and sell in exchange for cash
Yes, sir.
Checkpoint.
OK.
Good, the manager's here.
I don't know what that is.
Thank you.
Three colors.
It's like a signal.
Well, I...
I... I...
I like this one.
I'll share it with everyone.
I'm off!I'm off.
Bye bye!
Yum! Looks good!
Looks delicious!
Have him drink it now.
Have him drink it
Sweet meat.
Huh?
Wait, he's alive.
He's alive.
What's this?
Crab?
Looks delicious.
Lobster?
1,000 yen for today.
Arrow Street, Arrow Street, Arrow Street.
How much do you enjoy it?
I'd like to hear it. Two of us.
We'll have fun.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
It's not showing.
What's on your mind?
Durian smells amazing.
I've never heard of it.
Durian stuff.
I've heard of it.
I've never seen the real thing.
I was craving bananas.
I heard they're really good.
Let me know if you find some.
Okay, okay.
They're little bananas.
Goldfish?
Yes, ma'am.
Ceiling?
It's hard to get a good shot.Difficult to photograph
difficult to photograph
This coffee...
You want some briand?
Hey, that's a good idea.
What's briand?
Is it a sign?
What's that? It's the best in the world.
Briand.
I'll look it up.
I don't know, but he's the best in the world or something.
I know.
I knew it. "Briand.
Sign.
Sign, sign, sign, sign.
Band, the one we're doing from the band.
Thanks for your time.
See you later.
Um, you want to try some of this durian? Like that.
Yeah, yeah.
I'd love to.
Um, I'm thinking of trying durian for the first time.
It's only 1,000 yen.
1,000 Japanese yen is
3,000 yen.
What do you do with 3,000 yen?
What do you do?
One.
You want to go?
I'm going to buy durian.
I bought durian.
Wow.
I've never had durian.
You've never had durian.
No, I haven't.
Me neither.I don't have it either.
Still no scent, though.
I don't know.
This... is what you're famous for.
With this.
With gloves.
Like this with your hands
Eat it
Heh.
If you eat it
Will it stay for a while?
I didn't bring any water.
It's piling up.
Do you think it'll be okay?
I'm scared.
It feels so squishy.
It doesn't look like it just happened.
That's what it feels like.
Let's go.
Good night.
Oh, sorry.
I'm scared
Oh, I fell down
Ah!
Oh, the smell
Smell.
I don't know what it is.
But do I know what it tastes like?
I've had this.
It tastes like some kind of food.
It tastes like cream.
It's like... It's like a basket of dumplings.
I know!Oh, I know!
You know what?
It would be so nice if we could just roll it out this way.
It's like eating power with a basket of dumplings.
Yeah, yeah.
The power of the package...
One millimeter!
Definitely a millimeter right now.
Eat it.
The moment you eat it, the smell will leave your nose!
Durians are pretty expensive.
They sell them in the back for about 4,000 yen per ball.
I'm talking!
This amount of durian we ate was about 700-800 yen!
There are so many durians!
Thank you very much for watching.
I never thought I'd spend 1,000 yen on a durian.
I'm scared.
But I don't know yet.
There's still some left.
Let's look around some more.
What shall we buy?
I saw some skewers at the beginning.
The first one that looked good was delicious.
Let's eat it.
Let's eat.
I think we're almost there.
Wow!
Looks so good!
I love octopus!
I wish I could eat octopus.
Look at this!
It's huge!
Octopus.Octopus.
There's grass.
Fire?
How do we eat it?
Boil it?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Isn't that a frog?
Frogs!
But I want to eat a frog.
Frogs are delicious.
Frogs?
Frogs!
I've heard of frogs.
I know you're curious.
I know.
What? How long have you been listening to it?
Twenty-five.
Twenty-five?
25? 25?
You're...
Not enough.
Eat what you want, one at a time.
You're right, it's not enough.
I hear frogs are expensive.
Frogs are bad.
Here it is.
Do you want some fries?
Fries?
Frogs aren't very good, are they?
Sure it is.
How much?
Ten yen.
Ten?
10?10?
Precious 10.
Oh, great, they're letting me in.
I haven't even said I'd buy it yet.
Ha-ha-ha.
You work fast. You work fast.
I can't say no.
Thank you
Yes, thank you
I'd rather not
I'd rather
Well, well, well, there's a word for that, isn't there?
Bon appétit!
sounds delicious
Sounds good
ha, lie eat it!
oh, yummy!
delicious
what is it?
Spicy spice?
Yes.
Spicy?
But not too sweet.
It's like a sweet rice.
This is delicious.
It's delicious.
Tangy.
A little.
Hey, back there.
What can I say?
Is there a place like this in Japan?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Fruit.
Lots of fruit.
Fruit is the worst!Fruit is bad.
It's paradise.
I see bananas.
What?
I see bananas!
I see bananas.
How much for the banana?
It looks like a small banana.
Isn't that a little banana?
Tiny.
It's grass.
How much do you think it's worth?
Wait, is it cherry?
Let's buy some.
I've never had a banana from overseas before.
I've never had a foreign banana before.
I wonder how much they cost.
Three. - What?
What, five?
I can do it. I can do it.
It's a miracle.
A miracle happened... we bought bananas.
I bought bananas.
I bought bananas. I bought bananas.
I heard that the big bananas sold here are not from here
The small ones are delicious! Delicious!
It's only about the first spoonful!
I haven't done any planning at all.
They are tiny!
I can eat as many as I want in a day!
The skin is so thin!
It's so thin!
The skin is like onion skin
It's tiny!tiny
Tiny
Delicious
Sweet
It's like a chocolate banana
No chocolate, but it's like a chocolate banana.
Yes, it is.
It's good.
I'm a good eater, aren't I?
I'm good.
It's called a super Ronkonkot.
Yes, it is.
It's amazing.
Delicious.
Yellow.
Yellow?
I ate it.
It's sweet.
This is...
It's a good deal.
For three ringgit, it was a steal.
I still have a lot of it.
I'll pass them out to the members.
Shall we go?
Next.
Hello, hello, hello.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, we just met.
It's an exchange.
That's right.
Make yourself at home.
Thank you.
Can I eat this?
It's delicious.
Feel like a warm drink.
You still have 18 seconds.Still 18 seconds to go.
Eighteen seconds to go.
20 seconds to go.
You're lying.
Tell me you're lying.
And tell me...
I'm hungry.
I could do this for an hour.
One massage.
I can do it in one.
That's what I'm talking about. Negotiate.
What's that?
I'll be with my seniors.
Bananas.
Here.
They're so good.
We're going.
Bye-bye.
Bye, bye, bye.
Take care
Setup
Setup.
Okay, let's go frog.
Frog.
Frog!
Wow!
It was big.
They were all rotten and crunchy.
It just came out.
I didn't even see it before.
It was so big.
S'mores.
The last one was huge!
Oh, he's giving me a spoon!
Yay!Yay!
Here it comes!
I got enough
Oh, no!
Oh, shit!
Are you sure?
Who goes first? First.
If I can't go, I can go. I can go.
We'll be the first to go.
Can you afford it? Maybe.
So, who do you want to go with?
We'll play Janken, and whoever wins gets to go first.
In order of who wins?
Goo first, then rock-paper-scissors!
That's great!
Because I lost.
Last.
Rock, paper, scissors!
First goo, rock-paper-scissors!
All right!
I can afford it, I can afford it.
Oh, no!
This Ichichan looks so delicious.
I feel like a frog when I come here.
You don't like it now?
I like it.
Yes, please.
A little more, uh...
Oh, good, good, good.
Two.
Three.
Don't do it.
Goal.
Jump, jump, jump!
Goal!
skippingJumping
But it looks so good.
Can I try it?
It's so juicy.
It's kind of oily.
Not juicy.
It's so refreshing.
Juicy.
Delicious.
It's so good.
It's delicious.
Oh, my God.
Look at this.
Turn around.
Oh, my calves, my calves!
Oh, my God, her calves are so tight.
And the sides, too. Like the side.
Very bad calves.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
It's okay.
Oh, my God.
What time is it?
so...
I finished eating the frog safely
It was delicious!
31st
with ringgit
What a surprise!
We moved him up one place.
Yay!
It's a little bit like having Jyu and his friends here.
I'm so anxious, so anxious, so anxious!
I'm sure, I lost my money in the process.I'm pretty sure I ran out of money along the way.
It's gone, it's gone, it's gone.
They were handing out bananas and stuff.
I'm sure they had plenty of time to spare.
I'm waiting for second place.
Good luck.
Now, I have a request.
Do you have anything I can buy for 2 ringgit?
Two ringgit.
I'm looking for a foot acupressure.
You think 2 ringgit will get you a foot acupressure.
It's a really bad idea at this point.
That's really bad.
Five, right?
At least 5 ringgit.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'd like to find this one, but...
But 2 is hard to find.
Yes, sir.
No way!
There was a Bilingi or something!
Another one, maybe just this one with all this ice.
It tastes mediocre.
Hey, it's kind of a classic.
Perfect!
Next time!
Yum!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Pa-o.
What is this?
Is this...
Delicious.
Baby sponge cake.
You're eating the part that sticks out.
Oh, I know.Oh, I know
the way it is expressed
The way it's expressed, absolutely.
Yes, I know.
The crunchy part.
Yeah. - Yeah.
That was perfect.
It's so perfect.
So, here we go.
At Garrow Street.
For 1,000 yen
used up
No overage, no excess
I just managed to
I used it all up.
The first durian.
Almost done with the durian.
I finished it.
But still, not that one.
From 5 ringgit.
You know what? Buy a banana for 3 ringgit.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Revenge, right?
It was fun.
Bye bye!
Please subscribe to my channel and click the "Good" button!
Watch the next video too!
Bye-bye.
Thank you very much.